<resources>
    <string name="app_name">customCars</string>

    <string-array name="car_list">
        <item>Ford Raptor</item>
        <item>Volkswagon Golf</item>
        <item>Honda Civic</item>
        <item>Chrysler Pacifica</item>
        <item>Chevrolet Corvette</item>
        <item>Mercedes AMG</item>
        <item>Honda Ridgeline</item>
        <item>Dodge Challenger</item>
        <item>Toyota Corolla</item>
        <item>Mazda Miata</item>
        <item>Mazda CX5</item>
        <item>Ford Mustang</item>
        <item>Ferrari Tributo</item>
        <item>BMW M2</item>
        <item>Audi Q8</item>
        <item>Hyundai Veloster</item>
        <item>Nissan GTR</item>
        <item>Ram 1500</item>
        <item>Subaru WRX</item>
        <item>Porsche 911</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="fordRaptor_disp">
        It’s hard to not love the Ford F-150 Raptor. It can do the generic
    truck stuff like hauling lumber and sheetrock. It can also hit
    jumps and charge through the desert better than it has any right to.
    Most of all, you can get one today. Sure, the Raptor downgraded its
    exhaust note when Ford moved to the 3.5-liter V6 EcoBoost with its
    second generation, but that exhaust note sacrifice came with more power.
    The Ford F-150 Raptor will soon face some stiff competition from the
    likes of Ram with the 1500 TRX.
    </string>

    <string name="volkswagonGolf_disp">
        The Volkswagen Golf GTI is consistently one of the most fun-to-drive
        cars available, at any price point. While we’re in the middle of a
        generational shift for the model, it doesn’t look like Volkswagen
        plans to undermine what people love about the Golf GTI with the next
        generation. The current gen is powered by a turbocharged 2.0-liter
        inline-four making 228 hp and 258 lb-ft of torque. Most importantly,
        it offers a six-speed manual transmission.
    </string>

    <string name="hondaCivic_disp">
        Another low-priced entry into the list of the best cars available,
        the 10th-generation Honda Civic might go down as one of the best
        of the nameplate. If nothing else, it is one of the most versatile
        commuters on the market. Of course, you can take the Civic hatchback
        to its Type R top trim, if your pocketbook can afford the hit.
    </string>

    <string name="chryslerPacifica_disp">
        There’s no list of best anything if there isn’t a minivan present,
        and Chrysler’s revived Pacifica nameplate is one of the best you
        can find. Available with a traditional powertrain or a hybrid variant,
        the Pacifica excels in both trims. The hybrid does cost more, and it
        drops the glory that is stow-and-go seating but helps you eke out better
        fuel economy. Both are more than adequate at fulfilling all of your
        minivan-related needs.
    </string>

    <string name="chevroletCorvette_disp">
        $59,995. That’s how much a midengine, V8-powered sports car costs,
        thanks to the folks at Chevrolet. The eighth-generation Corvette
        has flipped the script on the ’Vette and finally dropped the engine
        behind the driver. The result? What might be the best performance
        bargain you’ll find, if you’re chasing a midengine sports car.
    </string>

    <string name="mercedes_disp">
        Prefer the engine in front? That’s fine, too. The folks at
        Mercedes-AMG offer one of the most interesting and fun high-end
        sports cars on the market today. With a 4.0-liter turbocharged V8
        letting your neighbors know you mean business, the AMG GT R is
        aggressive in every sense of the word. Oh yeah, let’s not forget
        that this is the hot-rodded version of the stunning AMG GT, a design
        that should age as well as the Mercedes-Benz 300SL.
    </string>

    <string name="hondaRidgeline_disp">
        Can you have a list without controversy? Some might look at the
        Honda Ridgeline and scream “That’s not a real truck!” That’s fine.
        However, it is a truck and fills the void left by the absence of
        the compact truck market. If you don’t need to move your whole
        county, the Honda Ridgeline should be good enough to handle the
        truck stuff without sacrificing any of the SUV comforts. It should
        be noted, I’m also a fan of Ford’s Ranchero and Chevrolet’s El Camino.
    </string>

    <string name="dodgeChallenger_disp">
        Back to the regularly scheduled programming. Dodge’s laundry list of
        Challenger packages is impressive, with the SRT Hellcat Redeye and
        SRT Super Stock at the top of its food chain. However, going down to
        the less powerful, and more affordable, Scat Pack trim might be the
        sweet spot for a lot of muscle car enthusiasts. More importantly, you
        can still get a six-speed manual behind the 392 Hemi.
    </string>

    <string name="toyotaCorolla_disp">
        If you’re not exactly performance minded or want to let the world know
        that you are an EV devotee, there is no better answer than the Toyota
        Corolla hybrid. Essentially a Prius in a Corolla shell, this hybrid is
        not only great on fuel but offers an outlandish amount of driving range
        for those who hate to refuel.
    </string>

    <string name="mazdaMiata_disp">
        Much like the Volkswagen GTI, you can’t have a list of best anything
        without including Mazda’s beloved MX-5 Miata. The Miata might not be the
        quickest sports car, but its lightweight and nimble nature make it an
        absolute hoot to drive. No, it won’t lap the Nürburgring in under seven
        minutes, but if you want a nice weekend driver, Miata is always the answer.
    </string>

    <string name="mazdaMX5_disp">
        Don’t worry, there are crossovers, too. The Mazda CX-5 fills the need
        for a crossover in Mazda’s lineup, while also being one of the more
        fun-to-drive crossovers on the market. Starting at just over $25,000,
        the Mazda CX-5 also punches above its weight in terms of comfort and interior
        quality, which only adds to its sound driving characteristics.
    </string>

    <string name="fordMustang_disp">
        The Ford Mustang Shelby GT350 might be a mouthful to say, but it’s worth it.
        While its swan-song final edition is here, and it’s not long for the new car
        lots, the Shelby GT350 might be one of the best Mustangs to ever leave a Ford
        factory. The 5.2-liter naturally aspirated V8 revs over 8,000 rpm and sounds
        incredible with its unique flat-plane crankshaft.
    </string>

    <string name="ferrariF8_disp">
        The latest in a long line of fantastic Ferrari sports cars, the F8 Tributo
        picks up where the 488 left off. Powered by a turbocharged 3.9-liter V8,
        you might not think it’s as pure a sports car as the Ferrari 458, but it’s
        hard to argue with performance.
    </string>

    <string name="bmwM2_disp">
        The BMW M2 (and its little sibling the BMW M240i) might be the most beloved
        BMW in the Autoweek office. Powered by a 405-hp 3.0-liter turbocharged
        straight-six, the M2 keeps the spirit of high-performance and driving-focused
        BMWs alive. Of course, it’s also no slouch when it comes to comfort, but its
        track-forward approach makes it a favorite.
    </string>

    <string name="audiQ8_disp">
        Another incredibly interesting crossover is the Audi Q8. While the concept of
        a coupe-ified crossover does sound like nails on a chalkboard to some, the
        Audi Q8 pulls off the style-focused look better than most. Sure, there is a
        slight compromise when it comes to cargo space, but sometimes style is more
        important than function.
    </string>

    <string name="hyundaiVeloster_disp">
        The Hyundai Veloster N is the freshest face to the hot hatch game, and it’s
        deserving of a ton of praise. Priced under the Honda Civic Type R, you get
        almost the performance brunt of the Civic for a lighter monthly payment.
    </string>

    <string name="nissanGTR_disp">
        The Nissan GT-R is on the older side of the new car world. But, what’s wrong
        with a formula that works? Colloquially called the R35 GT-R, this Nissan halo
        car does lack some modern tech features seen in other high-end sports cars.
        That said, it more than makes up for that with a race car feel and unbelievable
        performance.
    </string>

    <string name="ram1500_disp">
        The latest generation of Ram pickup might have reset what people expect from
        full-size, light-duty trucks. Its combination of comfort, space and utility
        make it a one-stop shop for those who don’t mind driving trucks daily. Its
        large infotainment screen and other tech comforts have turned the truck into
        a consummate tech marvel instead of a workhorse.
    </string>

    <string name="subaruWRX_disp">
        Without the Mitsubishi Lancer Evolution to push Subaru’s rally-bred WRX STI along,
        you might think that Subie would have just ridden its good name. Instead, Subaru
        has pushed the WRX STI further with limited-edition models like WRX STI Type RA
        and the WRX STI S209. While these special editions are costly, they do add tons of
        value to the base STI. If you can’t afford the high-end versions, worry not: The base
        WRX STI is a blast to drive all year.
    </string>

    <string name="porsche911_disp">
        Kind of like the Mazda Miata, you can’t make a list of best cars and leave Porsche
        off the list. With the new generation of 911 upon us, we still have a lot to learn
        as far as the higher-performance variants making their way down the pipeline. What
        we do know is that the latest 992 generation is, predictably, impressive to drive.
    </string>
</resources>